- Sorry, Raj. It's girls' night out.
- Maybe another time.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard:)Come on.
Girls' night. Girls' night. Ooh! Ooh!
(Stuart:)How does he not hear that?
(Amy:)What's the plan?
We gonna teach our fellas a lesson...
(Amy:)...by getting stinking drunk,
luring strange men into the bathroom...
(Amy:)...and turning the toilet stall
into a temple of the senses?
(Penny:)- No.
- No.
Jeez. Who's Forever 63 now?
(Raj:)Can we get another bottle of champagne
for the table? Don't worry, it's my treat.
- Thanks.
- You should come to girls' night more often.
(Penny:)And not just because if you weren't here
this would be a can of Pabst.
(Raj:)Nothing makes me happier
than the chance to spoil a lady.
(Raj:)Just ask my dog. My vet says
if I give her any more foie gras...
(Raj:)...she's going to die of gout.
- Hey, let's help Raj meet a girl tonight.
- No, no, no, I'm fine.